Guide to the Gerard Malanga Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- September 2006 acquisition, 1906-2005; 81.05; (102 boxes) + 2 art, 6 rolls, 4 broadside folders
  - " Ten Years After - 1st Draft, Typescript", 1966-1976 (Box 12)
  - " This Will Kill That - Essay, Final Draft Before Submission...", 1980 February 4 (Box 13)
  - "Fugitive Poems", 1965-1970, undated (Box 13)
  - " 10 Poems for 10 Poets, Black Sparrow Press", 1966-1969, undated (Box 13)
  - "Instituto Luce + Microstampa", 1968-1970, undated (Box 13)
  - "Herman's Empire Moving & Storage Co., Inc.", 1975, undated (Box 13)
  - "Impuse - Fear Issue (Toronto)", 1981, undated (Box 13)
  - "9 Photographers / Bellevue Press", 1980, undated (Box 13)
  - "A Portfolio of Photographs by Gerard Malanga of Writers Accompanied by Poems in Response to Other Poets' Choices of Photographs. The Paris Review, Winter 1975", 1976 (Box 13)
  - "Larry Rivers / The Ant's Forefoot", undated (Box 13)
  - "Parker Tyler", undated (Box 13)
  - "Alice B. Toklas", undated (Box 13)
  - " April Diary, a Film by Gerard Malanga / University of CT, Storrs", undated (Box 13)
  - "Photographers, et al", 1978-1986, undated (Box 13)
  - "Malanga / 100 Years Have Passed ", undated; 2 (Box 13)
  - A Handbook of Love Poems, undated (Box 13)
  - "Michael Findlay: 'Purdah and Other Poems'", undated (Box 13)
  - The Snowy Owl Shudders, 1973-1980; 6 (Box 13)
  - Possessing the Secret, 1975 (Box 13)
  - "Status + Diplomat Mag. 7 Issues", 1966-1969; 2 (Box 13)
  - "Artes Magazine / Gunnar Harding, Ed.", 1995-1996 (Box 13)
  - "Photographers Encyclopedia International, 1839 to the Present, Michel + Michela Auer", 1970-1993 (Box 13)
  - "Human Nature by Alice Anderson for Book Reviews", 1995 (Box 13)
  - "Jim Moffat, Art & Commerce", 1994 January 17 (Box 13)
  - "The Akashic Record", 1989-1994 (Box 13)
  - "Mark Salerno, Ed. / Arshile", 1993-1995; 2 (Box 13)
  - "Akus Gallery / Robbin Zella, Dir.", 1995 (Box 14)
  - "Business Plan: A Series of Erotic Books", 1983-1995, undated; 2 (Box 14)
  - "William S. Burroughs", 1988-1996 (Box 14)
  - "Carlos Blackburn, Poet", 1996 (Box 14)
  - "Gordon Baldwin, Curator - JPGM", 1993-1996 (Box 14)
  - " Mytholgies of the Heart by Gerard Malanga. Black Sparrow Press Draft / Master Copy", 1996, undated (Box 14)
  - "Bookings", 1990-1993; 2 (Box 14)
  - "John Martin / Black Sparrow Press Mythologies of the Heart Mss", 1995-1996, undated (Box 14)
  - "Agnes B. / Galerie du Jour, Paris", 1996 (Box 14)
  - "Babeth / Film Art, A'dam", 1993-1994 (Box 14)
  - "California SunCare Donald Christal / Gloria Heilman-C", 1996, undated (Box 14)
  - "Van Cagle, Author, Expertise in Glitter Rrock", 1996 (Box 14)
  - "Contrejour / Claude Nori, Sandrine Vincent", 1994-1996 (Box 14)
  - "Charles 'Chip' Carlson", 1994 (Box 14)
  - "Galerie J & J Donguy, Paris", 1991-1995 (Box 14)
  - " Good Girls, the Book. Letters, etc.", 1990-1994 (Box 14)
  - "Museum of Erotic Art / Copenhagen", 1993-1994 (Box 14)
  - "Fiction Inc. Makoto Ohrui, Tokyo", 1995-1996; 2 (Box 14)
  - "Lindsay Fass", 1995 (Box 14)
  - "Philippe Franck / Sub Rosa", 1982-1994, undated (Box 14)
  - "Karen Finley, Someone To Be Photographed", 1992 August (Box 14)
  - "Trevor Fairbrother, Beal Curator Museum of Fine Arts Boston", 1982-1993 (Box 14)
  - "Forbes Library - Northampton, MA. Exhibit Title: 'Portraits & Nudes / The Nude as Portrait'", 1993-1994 (Box 14)
  - "List for STEIDL Promo Booklet", undated (Box 15)
  - "1st Dummy - STEIDL", undated (Box 15)
  - "2nd Dummy Book Draft / STEIDL", undated (Box 15)
  - "3rd Proof Dummy - STEIDL", undated (Box 15)
  - "Delineation / Selection for Portraits Book", 1966-1983 (Box 15)
  - "Andy Warhol Museum", 1987-1996; 2 (Box 15)
  - "David Bourdon: 'Pop 1963' Chapters on Andy Warhol", 1987 (Box 15)
  - "Reva Wolf on John Ashbery", 1990 (Box 15)
  - "Reva Wolf Correspondence", 1989-1996; 6 (Box 15)
  - "GM Chronology 3 Drafts", 1993; 4 (Box 16)
  - "Gerard Malanga Interview for Vagabond (Ed. Bob Putnam, St. Louis - Oct. 12, 1989)", 1989 October 12 (Box 16)
    A related audiocassette is housed in box 16 under the title "Gerard Malanga phone interview by Maria Massey for Vagabond".
  - "Working Drafts, 'Lorna Hopper, April Playmate of the Month'...", 1990-1994, undated (Box 16)
  - "Emma Lovetere ne Malanga re: Embezzlement of Life Savings", 1990-1993; 2 (Box 16)
  - "Jim Dine: Original Cover Concept for Gerard's Book, Three Diamonds", 1982, undated (Box 16)
  - "Benedetta Barzini, Mirabella, Rebuttal to Oct. 1994 Feature", 1994, undated (Box 16)
  - "Letter to Jasper Jones, 17:vii:92", 1992 (Box 16)
  - "Benedetta Barzini / House + Garden Poem", 1992 March 27 (Box 16)
  - "Brion Gysin - Metaphoriconjunctions. 18:viii:86", 1986 (Box 16)
  - "The Anonymous Poem", 1992, undated (Box 16)
  - "Jean-Pierre Devresse, Artist", 1995 (Box 16)
  - "Balthus Fashion Concept", undated (Box 16)
  - "Passport to the Past: Packaging Concept for a Small Book of Erotic Photographs", undated (Box 16)
  - "PAST: A Photomural Concept...", undated (Box 16)
  - "Title: May 17, 1992 by Gerard Malanga. Tearsheets..." (Box 16)
  - "Title: Don't Get Angry. Get Even. Photo Concept Piece: Gerard Malanga 1:viii:92", 1992 (Box 16)
  - "Installation Concept, 15th St.", undated (Box 16)
  - "Joseph Beuys", 1986-1993 (Box 16)
  - "Exhibit Texts / Crawford & Sloan Gallery", 1993, undated (Box 16)
  - "Martin Deutsch, C.P.A.", 1992-1993 (Box 16)
  - "Why I Hate Lita Hornick? ... Because... etc. Drafts 1991", 1991, undated (Box 16)
  - "'Death...What Is It?' Working Drafts / by Gerard Malanga", undated (Box 16)
  - "Andre Malraux (1901-1976)", 1976 November (Box 16)
  - "Art Collectors / Art & Antiques Mag.", 1995 March (Box 16)
  - "Title: 'The Myth Continues,' 1992. Artwork by Gerard Malanga" (Box 16)
  - "Working Drafts", undated (Box 16)
  - "Paul Metcalf - October Min Anthology", 1990-1991, undated (Box 16)
  - "Aram Saroyan Essays", 1988 (Box 16)
  - "Interview w/ Malanga by Peter Headington, 1983", 1983 September 12 (Box 16)
  - "Steven Seymour - Gerard Malanga Documentary Project on Andy Warhol", 1991-1992 (Box 16)
  - "Nico Music Video Elektra Entertainment", 1990-1991 (Box 16)
  - "Views of the Narrows - Delineation for Panoramic Artwork by Gerard Malanga", undated (Box 16)
  - "Gerard Malanga Interview for Queer Magazine ", 1986 September (Box 16)
  - "Libby Himes: Term Paper on Andy Warhol", 1990 (Box 16)
  - "Bob Colacello", 1990-1991 (Box 16)
  - "'Commentary on the Present / Past Tense,' Drafts by Gerard Malanga", 1992 July (Box 17)
  - "Robert Creeley (w/ 3 Envelopes in Chas Olsen's Hand)", 1968-1996, undated (Box 17)
  - "Charles Wright", 1996, undated (Box 17)
  - "The Closing / 2 Anderson Street Gt. Barrington, MA 01230", 1990 April 4 (Box 17)
  - "'How They Didn't Meet,' Drafts", 1992-1994, undated (Box 17)
  - "'She Doesn't Remember' (1986)" (Box 17)
  - "Will the Real Andy Warhol Stand Up, Working Drafts, 26:iii:93", 1993, undated (Box 17)
  - "A.D. Coleman Photography Critic", 1991-1995 (Box 17)
  - " Mythologies of the Heart, Ongoing", 1990-1993, undated (Box 17)
  - " Mythologies of the Heart / Master Copy", 1990; 2 (Box 17)
  - " Mythologies of the Heart, 2nd Draft, Incl. May 2, 1991 Section", 1991-1993 (Box 17)
  - "Proofs: Mythologies of the Heart, French Translation", 1994 (Box 17)
  - "'Leaving New York,' Working Drafts, 1996", 1996, undated (Box 17)
  - "Title: A Newly Created Fashion Poem for Benedetta in 1992" (Box 17)
  - "'The Page-turner,' Drafts", undated (Box 17)
  - "'A History of Cambridge in 1982,' Poem...", 1982 December 4 (Box 17)
  - "Fugitive Notes for Stillbirth Poems", 1990 (Box 17)
  - "Kinderhook, the Series", 1990 (Box 17)
  - "Life Jumps (Working Drafts)", 1990 (Box 17)
  - "Title: 1990 (Working Drafts)" (Box 17)
  - "Forced Immortality (Working Drafts)", undated (Box 17)
  - "Poem in the Manner of Ted Berrigan. Working Drafts", 1990 (Box 17)
  - "Welcome Jessica Rock (Working Drafts)", 1990 (Box 17)
  - "Bright Light of the Berkshires, Working Drafts", 1990 (Box 17)
  - "'Willow,' Working Drafts", 1992 (Box 17)
  - "Poolside, for Jenny Thompson, Drafts", 1992 (Box 17)
  - "This Is Not a Poem for Tracey Trillett. Working Draft", 1990 June (Box 17)
  - "The Black Bra / Working Drafts. 1990. Gerard Malanga" (Box 17)
  - "A 6th Poem / Gerard Malanga. Working Drafts", 1990 (Box 17)
  - "Poem in French (Working Drafts)", 1990 December 1 (Box 17)
  - "Alex (Working Drafts)", 1990 (Box 17)
  - "First, What to Call this Poem. Second, What It's All About (Working Drafts)", 1990 (Box 17)
  - "What Makes the Weather? (Drafts)", 1989, undated (Box 17)
  - "The Photographer / Working Draft", 1990 (Box 17)
  - "'May 2nd (1992) One Year Later,' Poem by Gerard Malanga / Drafts", 1993 (Box 17)
  - "Dream: Hoe and Gerard Visiting Robert Moses, 22:viii:92", 1992 October (Box 17)
  - "'Dream with Ira 1:viii:92,' Drafts", 1992 (Box 17)
  - "Memorial Day (25:v:92) - Drafts", 1992 (Box 17)
  - "'In the Kaaterskill' / Working Drafts", 1992 May (Box 17)
  - "'All of this or Nothing' / Drafts", undated (Box 17)
  - "May 2, 1992 - Bk Mss by Malanga", undated (Box 17)
  - "Who! Loves! Ya! - Working Drafts", 1992 (Box 17)
  - "James Joyce Encounters Nora Barnacle in a Street in Dublin", 1992 (Box 17)
  - "'Say You Will,' Working Drafts 7:vi:92", 1992 (Box 17)
  - "For Leo (Castelli), Working Drafts", 1990 (Box 17)
  - "Boerum Hill and Milano / Two Sightings, Working Drafts", 1991, undated (Box 17)
  - "Poem / 'This Poem Doesn't Exist...' / GM", 1989, undated (Box 17)
  - "Poem / 'On the Verso Photograph by Aram Saroyan / Please Credit'", 1990, undated (Box 17)
  - "Poem / 'A Day Like Any Other,' GM", 1990 (Box 17)
  - "Poem in the Manner of Paul Blackburn / Malanga", 1990 (Box 17)
  - "Scent (for Sally Mann), Drafts", 1982-1989, undated (Box 17)
  - "'Wetlands,' a Poem by Gerard Malanga", 1991 (Box 17)
  - "'Walking Home thru Snow Blizzard from DIA Art FDN (6 Apr)' by Gerard Malanga - Working Draft", 1982 (Box 17)
  - "The Closing (Broadside, Ltd. Edtn)", undated (Box 17)
  - "Robert Mapplethorpe, Remember When. Draft of Poem by Gerard Malanga", 1990-1992 (Box 17)
  - "'L'Amour fou' - Working Drafts", 1992 (Box 17)
  - "'Natural Causes,' Working Drafts", 1992 (Box 17)
  - "'To Keep from Committing an Act of Terrorism Against the N.E.A. Lit Program,' Working Drafts", 1991 (Box 17)
  - "Children", undated (Box 17)
  - "Penelope Dickins Drafts, 1991", undated (Box 17)
  - "Babe Drafts, 28:viii:92", 1992 October (Box 17)
  - "Last Night's Dream, Working Drafts", 1989 September (Box 17)
  - "Kimberly Poems", undated (Box 17)
  - "From the Margin: Writings in Italian Americana / Correspondence", 1993 (Box 17)
  - "'Paul Jabara, 44, Actor, Singer, and Disco Songwriter...' / Drafts", 1992 (Box 17)
  - "'My Dream with Leo, 1:ii:93,' Working Drafts", 1993, undated (Box 17)
  - "'Morning of January 2, 1993' by Gerard Malanga - Working Drafts", 1993, undated (Box 17)
  - "'Some Medieval Troubador Song, 14:xi:92' - Working Drafts", 1992-1993, undated (Box 17)
  - "'My Dream with Ron Padgett, 17:iii:93' / Drafts", 1993, undated (Box 17)
  - "My Dream with Cindy Crawford, 21:ii:93", 1993 (Box 17)
  - "'Calvinized' for Josie Borain / Drafts", 1992 (Box 17)
  - "'Ideology of Vision,' Working Drafts", 1983 (Box 17)
  - "What It Is About Solitude, Is Like: Working Drafts", undated (Box 17)
  - "Eleanor Prior, Waitress. Charleston Restaurant, Hudson, NY", 1993 (Box 17)
  - "Poem / 'Hermaphroditismus Genitalis'", 1990, undated (Box 18)
  - "'The Longing' - Working Drafts, 29:i:96", 1996 (Box 18)
  - "Title: 'Once Clean Sheet, Full Moon, 16 May 1992, Gt. Barrington, MA' Artwork by Gerard Malanga" (Box 18)
  - "'If Looks Could Kill,' 18:vii:94 (Formerly 'Maia')", 1994, undated (Box 18)
  - " Mythologies of the Heart, Cobbled Working of Book Manuscript", 1971-1993, undated (Box 18)
  - " Mythologies of the Heart, 1st Concept MSS", 1990 (Box 18)
  - "Peter Riva, Literary Agt.", 1993 (Box 18)
  - "Aram Saroyan", 1991-1995 (Box 18)
  - "Harold Norse", 1991-1993 (Box 18)
  - "'Uma Thurman's Breasts,' Working Drafts", 1994 (Box 18)
  - "Velvet Underground Reunion Tour", 1993 (Box 18)
  - "The Velvet Underground - Lou Reed + John Cale", 1982-1995 (Box 18)
  - "'Uma Thurman's Breasts,' Master Copy", 1994 (Box 18)
  - "'A Champagne of Shoulders' 1994. Working Drafts. Revised Title: 'Are You the Dream of Duchamp'" (Box 18)
  - "Alexis Barth Poem / Drafts - 1995" (Box 18)
  - "Everything There Is To Know: for Alice Anderson", 1995 (Box 18)
  - "'This Never Happened,' Drafts", 1994 (Box 18)
  - "'You're It' Poem to Jaime Lee Curtis. Working Drafts", 1994 (Box 18)
  - "Hennie Waroux, Correspondence", 1993-1995, undated; 2 (Box 18)
  - "Beverly Pabst. Renamed Sasha Pabst", 1990-1996 (Box 18)
  - "Peter Moritz Pickhaus", 1993 (Box 18)
  - "Photographers - Letters", 1993-1995 (Box 18)
  - "Tony Pinck GM Exhibition in Martha's Vineyard", 1991-1993; 2 (Box 18)
  - "Arthur Hillman / Simon's Rock Exhibition Committee", 1993, undated (Box 18)
  - "Barry Savenor / Txt by GM", undated (Box 18)
  - "Else Lasker-Schuler - Inscribed Chapter by George Ball, Jr....", 1984, undated (Box 18)
  - "'Words' c/o Temple Press re: Ratio 3 Anthology", 1990-1993, undated; 2 (Box 18)
  - "Tracy Tillet", 1990, undated; (1 folder, 1 audiocassette) (Box 18)
  - "Lynn Tillman", 1994, undated (Box 18)
  - "Ultra Violet", 1993 December 30 (Box 18)
  - "Vincent Vallarino", 1989-1995, undated (Box 18)
  - "Michael Waters / Salisbury State U.", 1986-1993, undated (Box 18)
  - "Adam Weinber, Jedi's Brother", 1990-1993 (Box 18)
  - "Nina Zivancevic, Poet", 1994-1995 (Box 18)
  - "Gil Williams / Bellevue Press", 1993-1995, undated (Box 18)
  - "Vendors", 1990, undated (Box 18)
  - "Website Card Design Samples", 1999, undated (Box 19)
  - "Gerardo Malanga, Dad", 1977-1989, undated; 2 (Box 19)
  - "Arts New England. Charles Giuliano Interview, Transcript by Gerard Malanga", undated (Box 19)
  - "Arts New England. Charles Giuliano Interviews GM", undated (Box 19)
  - "Arts New England. Article on Andy Warhol by GM", undated (Box 19)
  - "Gerardo Malanga Estate", 1983, undated; 2 (Box 19)
  - "Checklist of Books by and about Andy Warhol. Collection: Malanga", undated (Box 19)
  - "Allen Ginsberg", 1989-1995, undated (Box 19)
  - "David Ignatow", 1993, undated (Box 19)
  - "New England FDN for the Arts. 1993 - Rejection", 1993 January (Box 19)
  - "John Chamberlain, Sculptor", 1986-1993 (Box 19)
  - "CAPS Grant Rejection - 1982", 1981-1982 (Box 19)
  - "Joseph Coplan aka Hoe, Co-author w/ GM on 'The Pool Book'", 1986-1993, undated (Box 19)
  - "Raymond Federman", 1994 (Box 19)
  - "Mary Flanagan, Novelist", 1980-1993 (Box 19)
  - "Ralph Gibson", 1989-1995, undated (Box 19)
  - "Jim Jacobs", 1989-1993, undated (Box 19)
  - "Frank Kuenstler, Poet", 1991-1992, undated (Box 19)
  - "N.E.A. Rejections", 1986-1995, undated; 5 (Box 19)
  - "N.E.A. Protest - 1986", 1981-1986, undated (Box 19)
  - "N.E.A. Corporate Funding", undated (Box 19)
  - "Notes for N.E.A. Poem - Concept Submissions", 1992, undated (Box 20)
  - "Aaron Sisking FDN - Reject", 1992 October 20 (Box 20)
  - "History of FDN Rejects", undated (Box 20)
  - "Chronology of G.M. Archives", undated (Box 20)
  - "Makoto Ohrui Fiction Inc. / THE DEEP Erotic Photo Gallery - Tokyo", 1994, undated; 2 (Box 20)
  - "Louis Behre, Other World Productions", 1994, undated; 2 (Box 20)
  - "The Journal of Erotica - Misdummer Books LTD, UK", 1992-1995 (Box 20)
  - "John Hersey, Jr.", 1993-1996 (Box 20)
  - "TCS Publishing Partners - Amsterdam", 1993-1995 (Box 20)
  - "H Magazine (Tokyo) Interview", undated (Box 20)
  - "Simon's Rock Writers Conference Proposal", undated (Box 20)
  - "Conceptual Ideas for Artworks", 1993, undated (Box 20)
  - "Conceptual Art", 1981-1983, undated (Box 20)
  - "Robert Creeley Conceptual Work", 1979 (Box 20)
  - "Pornography as Art Concepts", 1992-1994, undated (Box 20)
  - "The Crawford & Sloan Gallery", 1992-1993, undated (Box 20)
  - "Tom Bridges - Book Project Proposals", 1991, undated (Box 20)
  - "Julia Friar", 1990-1995, undated (Box 20)
  - "John & Vicky Perkins", 1992-1994 (Box 20)
  - "Zoe Reverdin, Dancer", 1994-1995 (Box 20)
  - "Chi Chi Valenti, Editor: Verbal Abuse", 1994, undated (Box 20)
  - "Children of the World Exhibtion Created by Gerard Malanga", 1993, undated (Box 20)
  - "Reva Wolf: Art Journal Article", 1966-1994, undated; 2 (Box 20)
  - "Two Girls in Playground, Copy Neg", undated (Box 20)
  - "Senators Jesse Helms + Joe McCarthy, Diptych Concept", 1990 (Box 20)
  - "Brooke Shields Concept Piece", 1992, undated (Box 20)
  - "Poetry Project Newletter 'Letter to the Editor'", 1994 April 5 (Box 20)
  - "Locker Room Collage", undated (Box 20)
  - "Fan Letters", 1993-1994, undated (Box 20)
  - "Eric Dahan, Journalist for Liberation", 1993-1995, undated (Box 20)
  - "First Intensity, Lit. Mag.", 1993 August (Box 20)
  - "Denis Deegan", 1994 March (Box 20)
  - "'That's Cory (Without the E)' Working Drafts", 1990 (Box 20)
  - "Bodyshaping / Kiana", 1993 February 3 (Box 20)
  - "Joseph Geraci, Publisher / Curator", 1994-1995, undated; 2 (Box 20)
  - "Alexander Steffen, Verlag Nishen", 1993-1994, undated (Box 21)
  - "Susan Minot", 1993 (Box 21)
  - "Lieberman & Saul Gallery", 1990 (Box 21)
  - "Saul Leiter, Photographer", 1993 (Box 21)
  - "Institut fur Popkultur (Wuppertal, Germany)", 1992-1993, undated; 2 (Box 21)
  - "N.E.A. / Censorship / Mapplethorpe, etc.", 1990-1991, undated (Box 21)
  - "1970s", 1970-1979, undated (Box 21)
  - "Crowns - Poems 1971-1972 Qabalah Poems", 1973 (Box 21)
  - "Edie Sedgwick, 1971-1972", 1973 (Box 21)
  - "The Immortality of Death (1970s)", 1975 (Box 21)
  - "The European Poets - 1970-71", 1971 (Box 21)
  - "Previously Published Benedetta Poems in Book Form", undated (Box 21)
  - "Poems 1972-1973", 1970-1973, undated (Box 21)
  - University of California Santa Cruz material, 1971-1976, undated (Box 21)
  - Poetry, 1970-1971, undated; 2 (Box 21)
  - "Poets on Photography Compiled by Gerard Malanga", 1978-1987, undated (Box 21)
  - "Poems by Gerard Malanga, Occasions 1970-71", 1970-1971 (Box 21)
  - "The Thunder Machine", 1966 (Box 21)
  - "Earth Wind & Fire", 1973 (Box 21)
  - "From The Snowy Owl Shudders", 1978 (Box 21)
  - "Unrevised Duplicates from a Precocious Poet, 1964-69", 1964-1969; 2 (Box 21)
  - "Gerard Malanga Is Available", 1970 (Box 21)
  - "Italian Subtitles", 1967 (Box 21)
  - "The Benedetta Poems", undated (Box 21)
  - "Chapters in a Life", 1976-1979 (Box 21)
  - "1970s & Berkshires Poems", 1969-1975, undated (Box 21)
  - "The Piper of a Sleeping Nation", undated (Box 22)
  - "Two or Three Girls I Once Knew", 1969 (Box 22)
  - Ratio: 3 Volume 1, 1991 (Box 22)
  - Untitled folders, 1970-1977; 9 (Box 22)
  - "The Bailey Bk Mss - 1972", 1972 February (Box 22)
  - "Collaboration: Anne Waldman / Lewis Warsh / GM", 1966 November 22 (Box 22)
  - "Orig. Folder Marked 'A Dream Book'", 1973-1975, undated (Box 22)
  - "Orig. Folder Marked 'Oneonta Poems' for Bruce Kurtz 1970" (Box 22)
  - "Orig. Folder Marked 'Gloss' Bk. Mss.", 1973 (Box 22)
  - "Orig. Folder Marked '1980s'", 1981-1983, undated (Box 22)
  - "Orig. Folder Marked 'Poems for Liz Denny Agnsta'", 1970-1971, undated (Box 22)
  - "Orig. Folder Marked 'Current Poems'", 1970-1983, undated; 9 (Box 22)
  - "Two or Three Girls I Once Knew - Draft", 1966-1977, undated (Box 22)
  - "Orig. Folder Marked 'Poems'", 1968-1973, undated (Box 22)
  - "Poems for the Fat Lady, ca. 1972-73", 1972-1973 (Box 22)
  - "Orig. Folder Marked 'Master Copy for Dup.'", undated (Box 22)
  - "Orig. Folder Marked Love Story (1971)" (Box 22)
  - "Mostly Bolinas Poems and Poems of the 70s", 1960-1974 (Box 22)
  - "Possessing the Secret, Part of a Mss.", 1969-1974 (Box 22)
  - "Gerald Hausman Mss", undated (Box 23)
  - "The Piper of a Sleeping Nation / and Other Poems from the 1970s", 1973-1979, undated (Box 23)
  - "Anti-Sonnets, a Complete Final Draft, by Gerard Malanga", 1963-1991 (Box 23)
  - "Anti-Sonnets Mss Duplicate Typescripts", undated (Box 23)
  - "GM: Chapters in a Life", 1976-1979, undated (Box 23)
  - "Assorted Poems, 1970s", 1971-1973 (Box 23)
  - "Orig. Folder Marked 'Poems for Circulation'", 1971-1976, undated; 2 (Box 23)
  - "'Rhapsody in Blue' (for Jessica Brackman)", 1983 July (Box 23)
  - "45-minutes About Silence", undated (Box 23)
  - "Filth", 1979 (Box 23)
  - "Sighting - Kim Yingst", 1980 (Box 23)
  - "For the July Program - Bennington", 1980 July (Box 23)
  - "Sitting in Crossett Library Looking out at the Green Mtns and Waiting...", 1980 July (Box 23)
  - "Lucky Strike", 1982 (Box 23)
  - "'Yourself' (for June Clarke)", undated (Box 23)
  - "The Aesthetics of Statistics", 1981 June 13 (Box 23)
  - "Gerard Malanga on the Subject of Beauty", 1983, undated (Box 23)
  - "Walking thru Snow Blizzard from DIA Art FDN", 1982, undated (Box 23)
  - "Edward Albee's Ear in the Manner of Allen Ginsberg", 1982, undated (Box 23)
  - "'A History of Cambridge in 1982' (for Rosie Blake Johnson)", 1982 December (Box 23)
  - "Photographing Jorie Graham", 1981-1983 (Box 23)
  - "'The Photograph as Destiny or Testing Jung's Theory on Synchronicy' (for Jessica Brackman)", 1983, undated (Box 23)
  - "'Sighting / The 9:15 a.m. to Dover Plains via N. Brewster' for John Hersey", 1982 June (Box 23)
  - "'...from May to December' for Steve Seymour", 1982 (Box 23)
  - "Joan Miro and His Daughter Dolores", 1983 (Box 23)
  - "Vagina Dentata", undated (Box 23)
  - "On Dying: 1981", 1981 September 12 (Box 23)
  - "November 10th 1979", 1979 November 12 (Box 23)
  - "'Rust Never Sleeps' - Drafts", 1979 (Box 23)
  - "'Ongoing Observations' for Wendall", 1978 (Box 23)
  - "Visual Dialectic", 1981 (Box 23)
  - "Sightings for Phil", 1979 June 12 (Box 23)
  - "Mudd Club", 1979, undated (Box 23)
  - "'The Same' (for Dennis Cooper)", 1979 April (Box 23)
  - "Malanga - Algeeirus (After Paul Blackburn)", 1979, undated (Box 23)
  - "Photograhy Wall", 1979 April 23 (Box 23)
  - "Lifeguard at the 'Y' - Hartford, for Hoe", 1979, undated (Box 23)
  - "Through the Looking Glass / Essay", undated (Box 23)
  - "Raffaella", 1980 (Box 23)
  - "'Soundside' for Molly O'Brien", 1978 (Box 23)
  - "Moon in Virgo", 1980 (Box 23)
  - "Why this Weekend in Particular?", 1979 (Box 23)
  - "A Shaking up of the Contexts", 1980, undated (Box 23)
  - "'One Year After the Knowledge of June 24 & 25, 1980' (for Stacey Asip)", 1981 (Box 23)
  - "'Between Moments' (for Stacey Asip)", 1980 August (Box 23)
  - "Poem to Andrei Codrescu", 1981, undated (Box 23)
  - "Lavorare Stanca", 1980 (Box 23)
  - "'Objects' for Jill Jacobs", 1979 (Box 23)
  - "Ray Dean Brock, 1929-1979" (Box 23)
  - "'Cooper Sq.' for Annie Luce", 1979 (Box 23)
  - "'Canaan Union Station' for Wende Case", 1980 (Box 23)
  - "A Very Important Lady", 1978 (Box 23)
  - "Two Variations + 3 Additional Parts", 1980 (Box 23)
  - "The Helen Review, Drafts re: Interview", undated (Box 23)
  - "Accabonic Hywy", 1979 (Box 23)
  - "26:vii:79 NYC", undated (Box 23)
  - "The Green River", 1980 September 1 (Box 23)
  - "Series II", 1979, undated (Box 23)
  - "Paralipomena, or Sundance", 1979, undated (Box 23)
  - "'& the Nude' (for Stacey Asip)", 1980 (Box 23)
  - "Let's Fuck", 1979, undated (Box 23)
  - "'Historical Emanation, 22:x:82' for Victoria Ruskin", 1982 (Box 23)
  - "Les Petites Fugues", 1979-1981 (Box 24)
  - "To the Future", 1979 (Box 24)
  - "Untitled Poem to Rachel Sherwood ('This Picture Has No Title or Date')", 1981 (Box 24)
  - "'Ceci Tuera Cela' / Epigraphy ( This Will Kill That ) for Assassin", 1971-1979, undated (Box 24)
  - "Weekend in Review", 1979 (Box 24)
  - "Odeon - Sighting", 1981, undated (Box 24)
  - "'Poem-Before-Epigraph (Poem)' for Jillian Nelson", 1987 (Box 24)
  - Accession - Refile in Proper File, 1983 (Box 24)
  - "Final Draft - This Will Kill That, Autobiographical Essay", undated (Box 24)